Isha Kothadia

Software Developer (.NET)

I have been working in the corporate culture since my graduation, and ready to accept the challenges, utilizing my technical skills, would like to work with a highly esteemed company which gives me a platform to use my expertise and skills for mutual growth and benefit of company and myself. Want to work on real life organizational environment to improve on my technical, business development and software development skills.

ishakothadia1000@gmail.com

Ahmedabad, India

(+91)9998969046

in linkedin.com/in/isha-kothadia-7b73ab1a3

EDUCATION

B.E. Information Technology Gujarat Technological University

06/2017 - 05/2021

Ahmedabad, India

- CGPA: - 9.48

Higher Secondary School (HSC) Gujarat Higher Secondary Education Board

06/2016 - 03/2017

Ahmedabad, India

Percentile: - 76.13

SKILLS



WORK EXPERIENCE

Jr.NET Developer

The One Technologies

08/2021 - 11/2022

Ahmedabad, India

- Assisting the development manager with all aspects of software design and coding.
- Attending and contributing to company development meetings.
- Learning the codebase and improving your coding skills.
- Writing and maintaining code.
- Working on minor bug fixes.
- Monitoring the technical performance of internal systems.
- Responding to requests from the development team.
- Gathering information from consumers about program functionality.
- Conducting development tests.
- Coordinated with team and worked with team work.

Internship

The One Technologies

02/2021 - 07/2021

- Debugging and testing code.
- Documenting and testing new software applications.
- Researching, investigating and fixing a wide range of technical issues.
- Collaborating with senior leaders.
- Approaching problems and creating solutions.
- Proactively learning about new technologies.
- Improved project understanding and execution skills.

PERSONAL PROJECTS

Health Wallet (07/2020 - 04/2021)

- Health Wallet is basically a Web Application where you can store your all Medical Details / Records / Prescriptions etc online.
- A health card is also provided to user which contains basic details of patient.
- Front End Angular, Bootstrap.
- Back End node is.

CERTIFICATES

Attended Cyber Security workshop at Ahmedabad Institute of Technology, Ahmedabad

Participated and was winner of Tug of War at Ahmedabad Institute of Technology, Ahmedabad

Participated in Filmistan at Ahmedabad Institute of Technology, Ahmedabad

Attended Meetup and Heatup for Startup workshop at L.D. College of Engineering, Ahmedabad

Attended Web Designing workshop at Creart Solutions, Ahmedabad

Participated in Creative Arts and Animation workshop at MAAC, Ahmedabad

Attended Cognitive Cruise workshop at SAL College of Engineering, Ahmedabad

Participated and was winner of Folk Dance in 7th Youth Festival of Gujarat Technological University, Ahmedabad